primalblueprint.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy – Primal Kitchen Help Center 888-774-6259

Primal Blueprint Support Staff 

Follow

Primal Nutrition believes that your privacy is very important. Read the following to learn all about our privacy policy.

Our policy applies to all personal information given and received, including all information from your past use of any of our products and services. We define personal information as anything that would identify you: your address, your phone and email contact information, your name, your preferences, your financial information, as well as other information that is not generally available to the public. Of course, this policy applies to Primal Nutrition and no other companies or entities.

Primal Nutrition does gather personal information about you when you register, use any of our products and services, or visit any of our pages or pages of our partners. We may combine information about you with information from other associates and partners.

When you become a customer or register as a member, we collect information about you, such as your name, contact information, birth date, gender, location, occupation and preferences. For purchases and some services we may ask for your relevant personal and financial information. Once you join, we know you—you are not anonymous. We collect information about your interactions with our partners and us. We do this automatically. Your browser also gives us your IP address and cookie information.

As you browse PrimalBlueprint.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, [AdRoll](http://www.adroll.com/ "AdRoll"), then enables us to present you with [retargeting advertising](https://www.adroll.com/retargeting "AdRoll - Retargeting Advertising") on other sites based on your previous interaction with PrimalBlueprint.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit [this page](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy "AdRoll Privacy Page") to opt out of AdRoll and their partners' targeted advertising.

What we do with this information: We do this to personalize your experience and to provide you with the service and/or product you request—nothing more, nothing less. This information allows us to fulfill your requests for our products and services, talk to you, improve our service to you and provide strictly anonymous reporting to other clients.

Children under 13 must have a parent or guardian approve registry and/or use of Primal Blueprint products and services. We will not contact children under 13 for personal information, sales promotions or marketing purposes.

We don’t rent, sell, give or share any of your personal information unless it’s to provide a service or product you request, or is regulated by confidential requirements. We value our relationship with you and we value your privacy. Your information is never made available without your explicit consent.

Primal Nutrition may need to set a cookie on your computer. Other companies that are not affiliated with Primal Nutrition do not have access to our cookies.

You can edit your account and preferences at any time.

We reserve the right to talk to you about matters related to your use of products and services associated with Primal Nutrition, including but not limited to announcements, service and administrative updates, order and account information, and health information.

You are always free to terminate your relationship with Primal Nutrition.

We provide complete physical, electronic and procedural security steps that comply with all federal government regulations in order to protect your information. We do not share your information with employees without their demonstrated, reasonable need to access your information in order to perform their jobs related to providing you with products and services that you request.
